- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
Kenny? Big spillage on table four. Sorry.
Okay. All right.
Excuse me.
Someone forgot this.
Oh, thank you!
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
- It's all right.
- She forgets everything. Thanks again.
She was some yoga teacher,
proper bendy. Look. Look.
Jesus! Fuck! What, she
sent that to you, did she?
Double naughty.
Jog on.
Linds!
Linds, where's my laptop?
- Don't be a bell end!
- Use your own.
- Mine's bust. Yours has gone all frozen.
- What did you do?
- I was trying to put on this film thing.
- What film thing?
Don't know. Some programme
lets you watch free films.
While I was trying to put it on,
then it locked up.
- Look, it's not my fault.
- Don't take it again. It's not yours.
- Oh, fix mine when you've done that.
- "Fix mine when you've done that."
_
- Stop nicking my Cokes!
- Whatever.
Did you draw that yourself, Kenny?
Thanks, Kenny. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
- Bye, Kenny.
- Bye, Kenny, I'll see you tomorrow.
You're mental.
- You're mental.
- You're a thief.
Love? Kenny? What do you think?
- I'm still not used to the colour.
- It's nice.
Yeah?
Do me a favour and prison-guard
your sister, will you?
I won't be late. Probably.
Oh, my God! He's outside.
There's a lasagna thing in the freezer.
I love you.
_
Have you seen my keys?
You okay, Ken? Love?
Yeah, fine.
Ha!
- Morning, Kenny.
- Hi.
_
- Kenny?
- Feeling really sick.
- You've only just got here.
- I know but think I might throw up.
Okay, just next time can you...?
Whoa! Easy, knobber.
_
Come on.
- It's fragile.
- What is it?
They told me to do that.
Is that it? What do I do now?
I can't really help you.
What do I have to do?
Just whatever they say and once
you've done that, you're out.
They let you off.
_
Hello?
Del... Delivery.
Wrong room.
They said 121.
No, there's no delivery here.
- But they said...
- I haven't ordered anything.
It's a cake.
- What cake?
- I don't know. I think it's a sponge.
I didn't order a cake so
just take it back to the bakery
- and tell them they got it wrong.
- Look, if I...
I don't want the cake.
So go away or I call the front desk.
_
I will kick that
cake up your fucking arse.
M-Mindy sent me.
- What is this? Where's Mindy?
- I was just told to give this to you.
- Mindy told you?
- No.
- You said "Mindy."
- That's what they told me to say.
Get inside.
So what are you saying?
Are you saying Mindy ordered the cake?
No, uh, I don't know.
It... they... it was them.
Them? They? Who the
fuck are you on about?
- The people.
- What fucking people?
The phone people.
The people on the phone.
They told me to bring the cake,
and they're leaving texts on my phone,
- and then I do what they say.
- Whoa, whoa. Slow down.
Just breathe through your nose.
Through your nose. Okay?
Good. Now, just show me what
they said. On your phone.
- Show me the text.
- Okay, well, um... This.
- I should...
- Shut up. Just let me.
What the fuck is this?
- Who are these people?
- I don't know.
- Who are you?
- I'm not them.
They send me messages,
and I do what they say.
Why? Why would you do that?
Is it them?
_
- They said I had to do that.
- Jesus Christ!
Okay, okay.
They're saying they just need
us to follow their instructions,
and everything will be okay. Okay?
Shit!
They're saying we have to do it together.
- What do we have to do?
- Just take the cake somewhere.
They sent me an address.
A map coordinate thing.
- And there's a car we need to get.
- A car? What sort of car?
I don't know what sort of car.
They said it's in the car park outside.
They sent me a licence plate.
That's all I know.
Why both of us?
I don't know!
Just let me deal with my
fucking shoe, please.
_
What have they said?
They say, "Go with him.
Take the package."
Okay.
"V760 DHM."
V760 DHM.
I'm getting fucking
number blindness here.
That's it.
All right. They said the
keys are on the back. Okay.
Look, maybe you better
drive. Do you drive?
- I mean, I had a drink back there.
- I can't. I can... I can drive.
I'm still learning.
Haven't passed my test yet.
All right. Uh... You're navigating.
Okay, you've got a sat nav on your phone?
Yep.
Here it is. Punch that in.
It's a street somewhere out of town.
Sort of High Wycombe-ish.
They said we got to be there by two.
It's gonna be tight.
So I'm guessing they got some shit on
you that they're threatening to put out?
With me, it's...
You saw the room, fucking lacy knickers.
I was waiting for a prostitute.
Escort, hooker, whatever
they call them now.
I got a family, which is great.
You get bored.
I mean, when I was young, I used to like...
I can't fucking justify it.
I just wanted to fuck a 20-something.
For old times' sake, I don't know.
I joined this website. I was curious.
Just wanted to see what was on there.
I got talking to Mindy,
who I thought was Mindy.
I mean, she sent me pictures.
I sent some back.
Phone photos. Grabbing my cock.
You name it.
They got the whole fucking thing.
But not just pictures, chat messages.
All the arrangements, where and when.
Me haggling over the price
and they say they got it all.
Sucked up the whole hard
drive like an audit.
Fucking twat. What a fucking idiot!
If that shit gets out,
that's my wife out the door.
Then there's the kids, she'll take them.
Oh, no, not a doubt in my mind
she'd take them and she'd win.
Custody, she'd win.
And I'm not losing my kids.
I tell you that right now.
No way! Absolutely fucking no!
They filmed me.
- Filmed you...
- Through my computer camera.
- What, like, filmed you?
- Yeah, like, you know, doing it.
- Like sex?
- No. Like, you... you know.
Jerking off. Jerking off
to porn or something?
Well, everyone does that.
- The fucking pope probably does that.
- They're gonna put it everywhere.
Like they're gonna send it to everyone.
- Oh, shit the fuck!
- What? What?
- How long's that light been on?
- What light?
Whoever's car this is,
they left it fucking empty.
I won't be a minute.
Unleaded. Unleaded.
Oh, bugger!
Listen, you pay, yeah? It'll save time.
Have you got any money?
Okay, Visa card PIN number 3109.
Say that back to me.
- Visa card...
- Just the number!
- Uh... 3109.
- Okay, go!
Pump four!
- What's your pump number?
- Four.
- You want some chocolate?
- No.
- It's two for one this week.
- I'm okay.
31.89.
Pop your PIN in.
- If you're sure you don't mind?
- No, no, of course not.
- I'll get on to that. Make some calls.
- Brilliant! It's next Wednesday.
- Okay.
- Keep it non-dairy just to be safe.
Okay.
This is, uh...
my nephew.
Nice to meet you.
- Kenny.
- Kenny. I'm Karen.
We're both Ks.
I'm head of the PTA at Theo and
Cassie's school, for my sins.
Just roped poor Hector into sorting
out the catering for the quiz night.
Been the usual balls up.
Listen, we better get this
guy to the station.
His train's... So we better go.
- Cansroad Station?
- Yeah.
Oh, couldn't drop me at the
end of my road, could you?
It's on the way. Mayer Street?
It's the bus otherwise and that
goes all the way around the common.
- We're in a bit of a rush, actually.
- Well, it's no detour. It's en route.
I'll hop out. Hardly need
to slow down. Yeah?
- Yep. Sure. Let's go.
- Brilliant. Thanks!
I'll just get in the back.
Oh, don't want to squash your box.
- What's that? Present?
- It's a cake.
- It's just a... it's a cake for Penny.
- Oh, lucky her.
So how is Penny?
Haven't seen her since...
must have been sports day.
She's good.
- She still planning to get back to work?
- Yeah. Yep.
_
- I mean, how old's Theo now?
- Uh... He's seven.
_
He was so funny in the play.
That big top hat on.
Yeah, he had a good time.
_
Oh, Anna's
having a sleepover.
Cassie's probably
already told you about it.
Six nine-year-olds in the house.
I must be mad!
_
So, Kenny, where you heading back to?
- Sorry. What?
- Are you going home or...?
- Uh...
- Train. Birmingham.
Yeah. Uh...
- Yeah, I-I live in Birmingham.
- Oh, my husband's from Birmingham.
- What part are you?
- South.
South.
- Mainly.
- Right.
_
Have you always lived there?
'Cos you don't sound...
I don't have the accent, no.
Everyone says that...
That... I don't have the accent.
Didn't grow up there though.
I grew up somewhere else.
Like London. I grew up in London.
Okay.
And is your mum and dad on
Hector's side or Penny's?
Someone crossing! Crossing!
Sorry about that! Can't miss his train.
This is me.
Great to meet you, Kenny.
Give my best to Penny, won't you?
- Yes, of course.
- Bye, then.
- Bye, Karen.
- Bye.
We're gonna make it, okay?
It's this junction.
- What? This one?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You sure this is it?
"Look in the cake."
Let's look in the cake.
Look in the cake.
In the cake, I suppose.
I got something.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
"Five minutes to decide."
Decide what?
- "Who is driver?"
- "Who is robber?"
_
Oh, no. No.
- W-w-we can't. We...
- I'm driver.
You said you can't drive. I'm driver.
I'll be right here with
the engine running.
We... We can't. We...
Then how else are we gonna
deal with this, Kenny?
- I'm not...
- Listen to me.
- Shut up and listen!
Hat and sunglasses.
No one's going to ID you.
You could be Kevin fucking Bacon.
That's point one.
Shut up!
Point two, in a robbery, staff are trained.
I am not...
They are trained to hand over the cash.
No argument. I saw it in a documentary.
No resistance. It looked easy.
It's not easy.
I know it isn't easy, but what the
fuck else are we gonna do? Hey?
This gets out, I will lose my kids.
And I swear to God,
I will stand in the kitchen
and put a fucking bread knife
through my throat if that happens.
- I only looked at pictures and...
- And beat one off on camera?
That's what they got, yeah?
Your hot little face, blurred fist,
dick burping fucking spunk everywhere?
Your mum's gonna love that on Facebook,
Twitter, Insta-fucking-whatever.
And her friends. All eyes
on you, giving it that.
Toss in the cunts at work,
calling you Spurty McGoo.
Laughing at your come face,
making it their desktop wallpaper.
It's not just weeks.
We're talking years here.
Pictures hang about on Google
like a gypsy fucking curse.
There's no cure for the Internet.
It would never go away.
It'd be glued to your name,
a fucking stain on you.
I'd hang myself if that was me.
Crack my fucking neck at
the first opportunity.
They just want the money,
so go in there and do it.
- You'll drive away.
- I am not gonna drive away.
I'm gonna be sat here
with the engine running.
I can't. I can't.
- You can. You can.
- I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
- You can.
- I can't.
We don't have much time, Kenny.
- It's not real. This is not real.
- You can do this.
Keep it together. Please hold it together.
- Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up!
- Okay.
Have you got a bag?
Glasses. Breathe through your nose.
Give me money.
Just give me money!
- Yes. Okay.
- Lots of it. I need lots of it.
Sh-should I use your bag?
Take it.
I'm going to pass this
back to you now. Is that okay?
There was some bloke standing
there on his phone freaking me out.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah.
Go faster.
Speed limit's 40. Wanna
get stopped for speeding now?
- Oh, shit.
- Fuck!
That's a siren.
Shh! Shush.
- Let's go!
- Shut up.
Wait, wait.
Come on.
Okay.
We're okay.
We should text them, no?
Tell them we got the money.
- They say we got to take it somewhere.
- Where?
This is it.
Yeah.
Here we go.
"Final instruction."
"Take car away and destroy."
Destroy the car.
"Just you alone."
Why just you?
_
I got to take the money
somewhere over there.
Why? Why have I got to do it?
Fuck knows.
_
So...
You better go, yeah?
Hey, you got this far, haven't you?
Just drop it off. That's it.
You'll be all right.
Hey, listen, Kenny. Look.
I'm sorry about... just back there.
Shouting at you. Calling you stuff.
I'm an all right bloke really.
I swear I am, when it's...
When stuff's normal.
You take care, yeah?
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, hang on.
They told me I had to
set this thing off first.
Okay.
You got the prize money?
- Prize money?
- You know, for the... fight?
How is there a fight?
- They didn't tell you?
- No.
We've got to fight...
...or else they post
everything they've got on us.
Winner takes the money.
We've got to do it.
I mean...
They're watching.
What sort of fight?
How do we know when it's over?
How... How do we know who's won?
I don't know about you,
but my life's over if this gets out.
Fucking over.
What they get you for?
I just looked at some photos.
That's all.
I just looked at one or two photos.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I just
looked at pictures too.
How young were they? In the pictures?
How young?
Yeah.
Well, me too.
Look, mate. Don't. Please.
Please.
Mindy?
Is that what you've become?
- A dirty, sick, disgusting pervert?
- Hey, relax!
Look at me! Is that what you are?
_
What did you do, Kenny?
They're saying it's kids!
That you've been looking at kids!
And Lindsey saw it.
There's a video of you.
All of her friends have got it!
Kids, Kenny! Tell me that's not true!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --